Do you think friendship is important
nowadays?
Yes, certainly.
Without my friends, I'd be very sad and
lonely, but they cheer me up and help
in every way possible.
Of course, all relationships have their ups and
downs, but we should definitely try not to
lose touch with our friends.
What do you think is the best time
to get new friends?
Hmm, probably the best time to get new
friends is your school and university years.
You have many possibilities to get in touch
with different people, and it is easier to
find friends with similar interests.
Is it important to stay in touch with
your friends throughout the years?
Yes, it's very important not to lose touch
with your friends.
Surely, everyone changes and even close friends can
drift apart.
But, in my opinion, friends are your second
family and we should highly appreciate them.